threewords.me 2014-06-18

# Privacy Policy — threewords.me

Last updated March 30, 2011

## Your privacy is critically important to us. At threewords.me we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We won't ask you for personal information unless we really need it.
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our services.
  * In our service, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what's visible to the public, kept private, and permanently deleted.

It is threewords.me's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please send an email to [contact@threewords.me](mailto:contact@threewords.me).

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, threewords.me collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. threewords.me's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how threewords.me's visitors use threewords.me. From time to time, threewords.me may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

threewords.me also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. threewords.me does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to threewords.me choose to interact with threewords.me in ways that require threewords.me to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that threewords.me gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a website at threewords.me to provide a birthday and email address. In each case, threewords.me collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with threewords.me. threewords.me does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

threewords.me may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to threewords.me. For instance, threewords.me may monitor the most popular pages on the threewords.me site. threewords.me may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, threewords.me does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

threewords.me discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on threewords.me's behalf or to provide services available at threewords.me, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using threewords.me, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, threewords.me discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when threewords.me believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of threewords.me, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of threewords.me and have supplied your email address, threewords.me may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with threewords.me and our products.

threewords.me takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. threewords.me uses cookies to help threewords.me identify and track visitors, their usage of threewords.me, and their website access preferences. threewords.me visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using threewords.me, with the drawback that certain features of threewords.me may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Business Transfers

If threewords.me, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that threewords.me goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of threewords.me may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, threewords.me may change threewords.me's Privacy Policy from time to time, and at threewords.me's sole discretion. threewords.me encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Acknowledgment

threewords.me thanks Automattic for writing a straightforward [Privacy Policy](http://automattic.com/privacy/) and making it available under the [Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike 2.5 Generic License](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/).
